plugin-alliance.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Plugin Alliance

Last Updated May 17, 2017

This notice describes the privacy policy (referred to as “Privacy Policy” or “Policy”) for Plugin Alliance, LLC and applies to the Plugin Alliance Service that is accessible at plugin-alliance.com (“Plugin Alliance Service”). This Privacy Policy applies to you, as a User of the Plugin Alliance Service.

PLEASE REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE USING THE PLUGIN ALLIANCE SERVICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH OUR PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE PLUGIN ALLIANCE SERVICE. BY USING THE PLUGIN ALLIANCE SERVICE OR SUBMITTING ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION OR CONTENT TO THE PLUGIN ALLIANCE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. Your use of the Plugin Alliance Service is also subject to the Terms of Service. Please review the [Terms of Service](https://www.plugin-alliance.com/en/terms-of-use.html) for additional details regarding your use of the Plugin Alliance Service. All capitalized terms have the same meaning as defined in the Terms of Service unless otherwise stated herein.

### Registration

During the registration process, you are required to provide your name and email address and you will establish a password. In addition you may opt to, but are not required to, provide your phone number, company name, and address. You agree to provide accurate, current and complete information during the registration process and to update such information to keep it accurate, current and complete. You agree not to share your password with any third party.

### Protection of Minors

Plugin Alliance does not permit children under the age of 13 to register on the Plugin Alliance Service or use any of its functionality for which registration is required. If you are at least 13 years of age but under the age of 18, you may use the Plugin Alliance Service but only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy.

### Information We Collect

#### Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

PII is information that identifies you or can be used to identify, contact, or locate you. For the purpose of this Policy, PII is defined as your name, home or business address, email address, and telephone number. Plugin Alliance respects your privacy. Plugin Alliance only collects PII through voluntary submissions, such as email, survey information, and online registration forms. The types and amount of PII collected from these activities will vary, but in no event will we collect PII that is not voluntarily given by you when using the Plugin Alliance Service. You consent to Plugin Alliance using your PII to facilitate requests, process payment information, contact you if a problem arises, email you information about our Plugin Alliance Service, or for other uses consistent with this Policy and your requests.

#### Unique computer identifier

Plugin Alliance collects a unique computer identifier upon registration of a licensed Plugin for authorization, security and fraud detection, and may associate your unique computer identifier with your email address and password solely for such registration, security and fraud detection purposes. You agree to the collection and use of your unique computer identifier solely for those purposes described in this section.

#### Other Statistical Information

Plugin Alliance collects statistical use data about your use of the Plugin Alliance Service, such as your purchase and demo history. This data is for your benefit and used in order to improve the Plugin Alliance Service and User experience, including alerting you of relevant promotions.

### Sharing with Third Parties

Plugin Alliance does not share any information with third parties without your consent except as provided in this Privacy Policy. Plugin Alliance may aggregate anonymous statistical data about Users’ use of the Plugin Alliance Service and share such aggregated, anonymous information with our third party licensors, but this information does not identify you personally and is not linked to any PII. In some circumstances it may be necessary to confirm your correct address for billing purposes with our trusted third party payment provider who is bound to confidentiality. Should Plugin Alliance merge with or be acquired by another company, any information collected may be transferred to and used by the resulting company. If Plugin Alliance were to cease operations, your data might be transferred to and used by another company, which offers similar or related products. If such an event occurs, we would attempt to provide you with continuity of Plugin Alliance Service. Plugin Alliance may be required to share a User’s information pursuant to a written request by a federal, state or local government authority, as required under applicable federal, state or local law, regulation or under a valid order issued by a court or governmental agency of competent jurisdiction.

### Third Party Links

We may display links to third party websites. You should always read the privacy policy of a third party service to find out more about how personal information is collected and processed on the third party website. Plugin Alliance’s Privacy Policy does not apply to third party use of your information. We cannot fully control how, third parties use your information, and we cannot be held responsible for third parties’ use of your information.

### Use of IP Addresses

As with any Internet-based service, queries to our Plugin Alliance Service transmit an Internet Protocol (IP) address, as this is what allows delivery of the information you requested back to you. We also use IP addresses for security purposes and to determine the approximate geographic location (the country or metropolitan region) of the query. We do not use IP addresses to identify an individual user by name, address or exact location.

### Cookies, Log-In Information and Opt-Out

When you are logged into your account, Plugin Alliance sends one or more cookies (which is a small file containing a string of characters) to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. Plugin Alliance uses cookies to help provide the best experience when using the Plugin Alliance Service. Plugin Alliance servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you log into your user account. These server logs may include information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, please note that if you do this you will not be able to use the full functionality of the Plugin Alliance Service.

Plugin Alliance utilizes the remarketing and targeted advertising services of third-parties, including Google and Facebook, to help Plugin Alliance create relevant ads. This means that Users and visitors of the Plugin Alliance website may be delivered ads for Plugin Alliance when browsing the web. These ads are tailored to the User or visitor based on pages previously viewed on the Plugin Alliance website. This is accomplished through the use of cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from the Plugin Alliance website and elsewhere on the Internet. Consistent with the cookie use described above in this Privacy Policy, the information recorded through the use of cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies does not include personally identifiable information.

If you own a Google account, please check your privacy settings within your Google account: If you have chosen to enable Google to associate your web and app browsing history with your Google account and to use information from your Google account to personalize ads, Google will use your data in combination with our Google Analytics data to build audience lists for cross-device remarketing (only when you are signed-in your Google account).

You may change your Google settings and opt out of these tailored ads from Google at <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en> by following the directions. To opt out or find out more information about the collection of web viewing data for interest-based advertising, visit <https://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

User Communications and Opt-Out

When you send email or other communications to Plugin Alliance, Plugin Alliance may retain those communications and related e-mail addresses in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our Plugin Alliance Service. In addition, Plugin Alliance may use your email address to provide you with Plugin Alliance news about products and/or Plugin Alliance Service and information about your user account. If you do not wish to receive these kinds of communications, you may opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe button located at the bottom of our emails.

### Legal Compliance

Plugin Alliance may disclose any information we collect if required to do so by law or under a good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the law or comply with legal process or to protect and defend Plugin Alliance’s rights, property, and customers, whether or not required to do so by law. Plugin Alliance reserves the right to contact appropriate authorities and disclose such information to them at our discretion when it appears that individuals using the Plugin Alliance Service are engaged in activities that are illegal or violate the Plugin Alliance Terms of Service.

### Secured Information

Plugin Alliance maintains a variety of physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your information and to deliver the features of the Plugin Alliance Service. While Plugin Alliance cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of your data will not occur, Plugin Alliance takes reasonable efforts to prevent such occurrences.

### Governing Law

This Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of California without respect to choice of law principles. You agree and submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in Santa Clara County, California for resolution of any dispute, action or proceeding in connection with this Agreement.

### Access to and Deletion of your Personal Information

In the event you desire to be informed of or access any PII we hold about you, you can email us at [info@plugin-alliance.com](mailto:info@plugin-alliance.com). You also have the right to delete your PII at any time. Please note, however, that once you delete such information, it may not be recoverable and you may not be able to access the Plugin Alliance Service.

### Data Retention

In the event your account is terminated or cancelled for any reason, we may retain basic contact and purchase information in the event we need to contact you about your use of the Service and for auditing purposes. This information is kept strictly confidential. All other information may, at Plugin Alliance’s sole discretion, be immediately deleted upon termination of your account.

### Privacy Policy Updates

Plugin Alliance will update this Privacy Policy as Plugin Alliance’s business and the Plugin Alliance Service expands and changes. You will be notified of material updates to this Policy by email with a link to the modified Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Plugin Alliance Service will constitute consent to the new terms. Plugin Alliance encourages you to review this Policy periodically for any changes that may have been posted.

### Questions

If you have any questions, comments or feedback about Plugin Alliance’s use of your information or about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [info@plugin-alliance.com](mailto:info@plugin-alliance.com). Plugin Alliance will use reasonable efforts to promptly investigate any complaint you may have regarding our use of your information.
